<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</title>
    <link>/findings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Findings on UVA Biocomplexity Institute</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/findings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>General Project Overview</title>
      <link>/findings/general-overview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/general-overview/</guid>
      <description>While this page is optional, it probably makes sense to have one weighted at the top (see the front matter at the top of this Rmd file) that gives a general overview of the project. This could be something like the final poster while the other pages highlight more in-depth observations. Here is a general schema of what should be covered throughout your website:
Main Findings [Here you will describe the results and include important visualizations from your project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Profiling and Benchmarking</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-one/</guid>
      <description>/* this chunnk of code centers all of the headings */ h1, h2, h3 { text-align: center; }  Examples Page If you want to add in an image on an Rmd file, use this link here. It ends up being a little tricky, but as long as you have created a folder to insert your images, you can just use some markdown code or html to insert images in the format you want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequence Exploration</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-two/</guid>
      <description>Exploring veteran&#39;s whole career sequences After cleaning the BGT data, we created our sequence objects using TraMineR. To begin, we created a sequence object using the whole career of veterans. This yielded 8,068 sequences of varying lengths. When creating the whole career sequence object, we defined eight unique states: Zone 1, Zone 2, Zone 3, Zone 4, Zone 5, Missing zone, Military, and Unemployed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sequence Clustering</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-clustering/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-clustering/</guid>
      <description>In the previous Sequence Exploration, we introduced the following sequence state naming system, shown in Table 1.
 {&#34;x&#34;:{&#34;filter&#34;:&#34;none&#34;,&#34;data&#34;:[[&#34;Zone 1&#34;,&#34;Zone 2&#34;,&#34;Zone 3&#34;,&#34;Zone 4&#34;,&#34;Zone 5&#34;,&#34;Missing zone&#34;,&#34;Military&#34;,&#34;Unemployed&#34;,&#34;Military transition unemployed&#34;,&#34;Civilian unemployed&#34;,&#34;Retired&#34;],[&#34;Z1&#34;,&#34;Z2&#34;,&#34;Z3&#34;,&#34;Z4&#34;,&#34;Z5&#34;,&#34;MISSING&#34;,&#34;MILITARY&#34;,&#34;UNEMP&#34;,&#34;TR UNEMP&#34;,&#34;CV UNEMP&#34;,&#34;RETIRED&#34;],[&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;O*NET SOC Code&#34;,&#34;seqdef() gaps =&#34;,&#34;seqdef() left =&#34;,&#34;seqdef() gaps =&#34;,&#34;seqdef() right =&#34;],[&#34;Job Zones group occupations into one of five categories based on levels of education, experience, and training necessary to perform the occupation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tournament Theory</title>
      <link>/findings/results-section-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/findings/results-section-four/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>